So I'm going to click into my Population_Segmentation_Exercise notebook.
打开 Pop_Segmentation_Exercise notebook
So the first thing I want to do is make sure I'm operating in the correct kernel.
首先确保在正确的内核下操作
So I'll go to "Kernel", "Change kernel",
转到“Kernel”&gt;“Change kernel”
and I can see that SageMaker offers a variety of different kernels to operate in.
可以看到 SageMaker 提供了各种内核
For all of these examples,
对于所有这些示例
we'll either use conda_mxnet_p36 or conda_pytorch_p36.
我们将使用 conda_mxnet_p36 或 conda_pytorch_p36
This indicates the type of deep learning frameworks that we might use.
这个表示我们会使用的深度学习框架类型
Mxnet is the one that's built into SageMaker,
mxnet 是 SageMaker 内置的学习框架
and p36 indicates the version of Python we'll be using.
p36 表示我们将使用的 Python 版本
So for this example,
对于此示例
we'll be using built-in algorithms and using mxnet_p36 will be the ideal kernel.
我们将使用内置算法 而 mxnet_p36 将是理想的内核
I can check which kernel I'm in by looking at the top right corner of my notebook.
我可以在 notebook 的右上角查看我使用的是哪个内核
For the segmentation example I should note that
对于这个分割示例 需要注意的是
my strategy will be to go over this first notebook in great detail.
我将详细讲解第一个 notebook
As we go through examples,
当我们讲解这些示例时
I'll transfer more and more responsibility to you,
越来越多的任务将交给你
leaving it up to you to complete the code,
需要你来完成代码
but I'll always provide a final solution notebook.
但是我始终会提供最终解答 notebook
Now, you can read a bit about the US census dataset
这部分介绍了美国人口普查数据集
here and the overall approach I plan to take to segment this data.
以及为了分割此数据集我将采取的总体方法
This notebook is really a modified version of
此 notebook 是一篇 SageMaker 博文中
code that comes from a SageMaker blog post linked here.
代码的修改版本 这是这篇博文的链接
In this notebook, you'll employ to
在此 notebook 中
unsupervised learning algorithms to do population segmentation.
你将使用两个非监督式学习算法进行人口细分
This aims to find natural groupings and population data and
目标是查找人口数据中的自然分组
reveal some feature level similarities between different regions in the US.
并发现美国不同区域的特征级相似性
To implement population segmentation,
为了实施人口细分
you'll go through a number of steps.
你需要完成几个步骤
First, data loading and exploration,
首先 加载和探索数据
then data cleaning and preprocessing.
然后清理和预处理数据
After cleaning your data,
清理数据后
you'll move on to dimensionality reduction with PCA.
通过 PCA 降维
PCA stands for Principal Component Analysis.
PCA 是主成分分析的缩写
You'll use these components to create
你将利用这些成分
new features and transform your original training data.
创建新的特征并转换原始训练数据
Finally, you'll cluster your transformed data using a k-means clustering algorithm.
最后 使用 K 均值聚类算法聚类转换的数据
We'll also get a lot of practice visualizing what each of these models,
我们还将练习可视化每个模型
PCA and k-means, has learned to do.
PCA 和 K 均值学习的规律
Meaning we'll take a look at the components and
我们将查看这些模型生成的
the k clusters that are produced by these models.
成分和 K 聚类
Each of the exercises in this notebook are designed to give you
这个 notebook 中的每道练习
practice with each step of the ML workflow and to
旨在帮助你练习机器学习工作流程的每个步骤
demonstrate how to use SageMaker tools such as
并展示如何使用 SageMaker 工具
data management with S3 and SageMaker's built-in algorithms.
例如通过 S3 管理数据以及使用 SageMaker 的内置算法
So the first couple of cells you'll see in here are loading a bunch of libraries,
前几个单元格将加载各种库
some for visualization and some that are specific to SageMaker,
有些是可视化库 有些是 SageMaker 库
specifically, the boto3 and SageMaker libraries.
包括 boto3 和 SageMaker 库
SageMaker has many libraries installed so you often just have to import
SageMaker 安装了很多库 通常你只需指向要使用的资源
the resources you want much like in the workspaces in the Udacity classroom.
就像在优达学城教室的 workspace 中一样
Now, we can get the data.
下面获取数据
This particular dataset is already in an Amazon S3 bucket and
这个数据集已经位于 Amazon S3 存储桶中
I can load the data by pointing to this bucket and getting a data file by name.
我可以通过指向这个存储桶加载数据 并通过名称获取数据文件
So first, I'll have to create a boto3 client to interact with S3.
首先需要创建一个与 S3 交互的 boto3 客户端
Now, if I run this cell and I did this correctly,
如果代码输入正确 然后运行此单元格
I should be able to look at a list of objects in that bucket.
应该会看到该存储桶中的对象列表
So here, I'm calling my client asking it to list
我在这里调用该客户端
all the objects that are in my bucket and then printing out the contents of that bucket.
要求它列出存储桶中的所有对象 然后输出该存储桶中的内容
I can see there's just one file in here, Census_Data_for_SageMaker.
可以看到其中只有一个文件 Census_Data_for_SageMaker
It's a CSV file and I'm just going to get that one name.
它是一个 CSV 文件 获取该名称
So I have the name of the CSV file that I want to retrieve.
我获得了要检索的 CSV 文件的名称
To actually get an S3 object,
要获取 S3 对象
I'm going to call our client again and call get_object,
我将再次调用 client 并调用 get_object
passing it in the bucket,
传入该存储桶以及键
and the key which is the file name I just saved from here.
键就是我在这里保存的文件名
In this last line, I'm printing out what the data object contains.
在最后一行 我输出了 data_object 包含的内容
So this object actually holds a lot of metadata
这个对象包含大量元数据
including things like the content type which is a CSV file here.
例如 content-type 是一个 csv 文件
At the end, I see this body tag and a label streaming body here.
在最后有个 Body 标记 这里是 StreamingBody 标记
This streaming data is exactly what I want.
我要的就是这个 Streaming 数据
So in the next cell, I'm going to access that body,
在下个单元格 我将访问该 Body
read it in, and print out it's data type.
读取它并输出数据类型
I can see that the datatype is bytes which I can read in with a call to io.BytesIO.
数据类型是 bytes 我可以通过调用 io.BytesIO 读取它
This will finally give me a data stream that I can read in just like
最终获得一个像读取 csv 文件一样读取的 data_stream
a CSV file and create a dataframe of county information.
并创建一个包含郡县信息的 dataframe
So that was the number of steps to read in a data stream from an S3 bucket.
这些就是从 S3 存储桶中读取 data_stream 的步骤
But I really just wanted to show you how to load in any data from an S3 bucket.
你可以按照这些步骤从 S3 存储桶中加载任何数据
Later, you'll see that you can also directly download data from the web.
稍后 你会发现你可以直接从网络上下载数据
So I'm loading the data and I'm taking a quick look at what's held in the CSV file.
我加载了数据并快速查看了 csv 文件里的内容
Just printing out the head or the first five rows of data,
输出标题和前五行数据
I see a census ID, a state and county,
包括 Censusid state county
and a lot of other features that look like they're counting up people
以及很多其他特征 这些特征列出了
and percentages for different demographic characteristics for that county.
郡县的不同人口特征的人数和百分比
The census records traits like total population,
人口普查记录特征包括总人口
race, transportation methods, and labor statistics.
种族 交通工具和劳动力统计信息
These traits have even changed over time as ideas of population categories change.
这些特性随着时间的推移已经改变了 因为人口类别改变了
As with any population data,
与任何人口数据一样
the traits paint a simplified picture of
这些特性简单地描绘了美国人口
the US population and real life is not as clean as this data.
但是实际情况并不是这么简单清晰
That being said, looking at commonalities or differences between
话虽这么说 但是查看区域之间的相似性或不同之处
regions can give you some really interesting and useful information.
可以提供一些很有趣实用的信息
Now that we've loaded in the data,
加载了数据后
it's time to clean it up,
下面清理
explore it, and preprocess it.
探索和预处理数据
When you first explore any data,
在首次探索任何数据时
it's good to know what you're working with,
有必要了解下将使用的数据
how many data points and features are you starting with,
一开始有多少数据点和特征？
and what kind of information can you get at a first glance?
一眼看去可以得出什么样的信息？
So you should investigate the shape of the data
你应该查看数据的形状
and I want you to implement a simple data cleaning step.
在第一道练习中
Your first exercise.
你需要完成简单的数据清理步骤
This will be to drop any incomplete data points.
即删除任何不完整的数据点
So any data with any columns missing or
任何缺少列或列为空的数据
empty should not be included in the final training set.
都不应该包含在最终训练集中
After you drop any incomplete data,
删除任何不完整的数据后
I want you to do some data preprocessing.
请预处理数据
Eventually, you want to feed these features into a machine learning model.
最终 你需要将这些特征传入机器学习模型中
ML models need numerical data to learn from
机器学习模型需要从数值数据中学习规律
and not categorical data like strings like state and county.
而不是类别数据 例如 state 和 county 等字符串
So you'll reformat this data such that the data is
你需要调整这些数据的格式
indexed by region, specifically, by "State-County".
使其按照区域“State-County”设定索引
Then, you'll drop the old state and county columns along with the census ID column,
然后需要删除旧的 state 和 county 列 以及 Censusid 列
which is just an assigned number and doesn't give us any demographic info.
Censusid 只是一个编号 不包含任何人口信息
So instead of having row indices,
现在数据没有行索引
this data will now be indexed by
而是按照 State-County 设定索引
state-county and the rest of the features can remain as columns here.
剩下的特征列保持不变
After completing your code,
编写完代码后
you should get a dataframe whose start looks a bit like this.
你应该获得开头如下所示的 dataframe
Basically, you want a clean dataframe with
这是一个整洁的 dataframe
no empty columns of useful numerical regional features to compare.
没有空列 并且都是可以相互比较的实用数值区域特征
If you complete all this code,
如果你完成了所有这些代码
you can move on to some interesting visualizations later on in the notebook.
可以继续转到后面的可视化部分
I also want to note that you should make sure to use
注意 你应该使用给定的变量名
the given variable names as they may be referenced later on in this notebook.
因为稍后在此 notebook 中可能会引用这些变量名
I'm assuming that you'll execute all of these cells in order, and for example,
我假定你按顺序执行了所有这些单元格
clean_counties_df, which should look like this final clean counties dataframe,
例如 clean_counties_df 应该是这样的整洁郡县 dataframe
will be referenced later on in this notebook.
稍后将在此 notebook 中引用 clean_counties_df
If you get stuck on either the cleaning or
如果你在清理或转换格式练习中遇到问题
reformatting exercises or just want to check your work,
或者想检查你的代码
you can consult my solution video next.
请观看下个解答视频